{"response_code": 0, "results": [{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "question": "Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.", "difficulty": "medium", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "question": "In the &quot;Shrek&quot; film franchise, Donkey is played by Eddie Murphy.", "difficulty": "easy", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "question": "The first televised presidential debate was between Jimmy Carter and Gerald Ford.", "difficulty": "medium", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "question": "The colour of the pills in the Matrix were Blue and Yellow.", "difficulty": "medium", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.", "difficulty": "easy", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "question": "The 2005 video game &quot;Call of Duty 2: Big Red One&quot; is not available on PC.", "difficulty": "easy", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "question": "The Platypus is a mammal.", "difficulty": "medium", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "question": "&quot;Cube&quot;, &quot;Cube 2: Hypercube&quot; and &quot;Cube Zero&quot; were directed by the same person.", "difficulty": "hard", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "question": "A caterpillar has more muscles than humans do.", "difficulty": "easy", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "question": "In World War ll, Great Britian used inflatable tanks on the ports of Great Britain to divert Hitler away from Normandy/D-day landing.", "difficulty": "easy", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]}